<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Homiefy</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">92431922154-vraiphkepcpi6gbk2b4u584eu8a1fd6l.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>


    <string-array name="report_reasons">
        <item>Select issue type</item>
        <item>Miss information</item>
        <item>Unreasonable price</item>
        <item>Room is no longer available</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="payment_methods">
        <item>Select method</item>
        <item>Credit Card</item>
        <item>MoMo</item>
        <item>Bank Transfer</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="issue_types">
        <item>Select issue type</item>
        <item>App crashes</item>
        <item>Feature not working</item>
        <item>UI/UX issue</item>
        <item>Performance problem</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="support_question_prompt">Have a question? Ask us!</string>
    <string name="chat_with_support">Chat with Support</string>
    <string name="submit_request">Submit Request</string>
    <string name="send_message">Send</string>

    <string name="contract_terms">
        ARTICLE 1: OBJECT AND TERM OF RENTAL\n
- Party A agrees to rent the room to Party B and Party B agrees to rent the room according to the information stated above.\n
- Rental period: 06 months from the date of signing the contract.\n\n

ARTICLE 2: RENTAL PRICE AND PAYMENT METHOD\n
- Room rent is paid on the 5th of each month.\n
- Electricity bill: Calculated by separate meter, unit price according to electricity regulations.\n
- Water bill: Calculated by separate meter or agreed rate.\n
- The deposit will be refunded upon termination of the contract if there is no property damage.\n\n

ARTICLE 3: RESPONSIBILITIES OF PARTY A\n
- Ensure the legal right to use the room for Party B.\n
- Repair any damage not caused by Party B.\n
- Notify at least 30 days in advance if there is any change in the rental price.\n\n

ARTICLE 4: RESPONSIBILITIES OF PARTY B\n
- Use the room for the right purpose, keep it clean.\n
- Pay the rent and service fees in full and on time.\n
- Do not arbitrarily repair or renovate the room without the consent of Party A.\n
- Notify 30 days in advance if you want to terminate the contract before the deadline.\n\n

ARTICLE 5: TERMINATION OF THE CONTRACT\n
- The contract terminates in the following cases:\n
+ The lease term expires\n
+ The two parties agree to terminate the contract\n
+ Serious violation of the agreed terms\n\n

ARTICLE 6: GENERAL PROVISIONS\n
- The two parties commit to comply with the terms of the contract.\n
- Any disputes will be resolved in a spirit of reconciliation.\n
- The contract is effective from the date of confirmation by both parties.\n
    </string>


</resources>